e-careers.com 2016-12-23

# e-Careers - Privacy Policy

e-Careers Limited respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how e-Careers Limited uses and protects any information we collect and how we use it. Please make a note that by using and accessing this website you are consenting to the collection and processing of data referred to in this policy and as amended from time to time by us.

##### WHAT WE COLLECT

We may collect, store and use the following information:

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address and telephone numbers.
  * Demographic information such as postcodes, preferences, interests and hobbies.
  * Information about your computer including your IP address, browser type, operating system etc.
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and / or offers.

Please note that the above such information may be collected via various ways when you register yourselves with our website, request any information, participate in surveys, promotions or any other feature of this website. Further the information might be collected by using common online collection methods like web browser cookies and other common tools. Moreover we collection information via third parties like social media websites (Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, Linked In etc.) that you connect to may give us information about you.

##### WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER

We may use your personal information to:

  * To respond to your questions and requests.
  * To provide you with access to certain areas and features of this website.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * To administer our website.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information including the businesses of carefully selected third parties which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

##### DISCLOSING PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents and suppliers so far as necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.
  * We may disclose your personal information to the extent that we are required to do so by law and / or in connection with any current or future legal proceedings.

It is to be noted that except as provided in this policy, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties. However please be aware that since some of the courses that you buy are sourced by us and provided via our supplier’s Learning Management System (LMS), we will need to share certain details of yours in order to provide you, access to the course and fulfil our services.

##### CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The information provided might be used for the different purposes as explained above. However please note that at the time of collection of information for particular purposes like promotional offers and marketing campaigns, an ‘opt-out’ option would be available depending on different circumstances. An opt-out option means you indicate that you do not want us to send any communication regarding various promotional offers and various other marketing campaigns and product information. If you have opted for the opt-out option, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of the website. Moreover if you have previously agreed to us to use your personal information for such communication purposes, you have option to change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@e-careers.com](mailto:info@e-careers.com)

You may request details of your personal information for small fee (£10) payable which we hold under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like to have a copy of the information held on you please write to:

e-Careers Limited, Unit 6, Waterside Drive, Langley, SL3 6EZ, UK.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or e-mail us as soon as possible, at the above mentioned address.

##### SECURITY OF THE INFORMATION

We at e-Careers Limited are committed to ensuring your information is secure and for this purpose we have taken certain standard security measures. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However please note that we cannot give absolute guarantee or promise the security of the information since internet is a public place. To the fullest extent permitted by law, we disclaim all liability and responsibility for any loss, damage, liability or any cost you may suffer due to any loss, unauthorised access, misuse or alteration of any information you submit to this website.

##### HOW WE USE COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse the traffic and knows when you visit a particular website. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Cookies helps us to analyse data about the website traffic and improve our website.

Please make a note that a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any other data of yours, other than the information which is shared by you to us. Furthermore, you may choose to accept or decline cookies however one must note that some web browsers automatically accept cookies. But you may log-in to your web browser settings and amend the settings to decline cookies if you prefer to. In case you opt for this option, you might not be able to take full advantage of the website.

##### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to the other websites of interest that we do not own or operate. So once you have used this links to leave our website, you should note that we do not have any control over the other such websites. Therefore we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such websites and they are not governed by the privacy policy of e-Careers Limited. You should exercise caution and independently assess the privacy policy of the website in question.

##### DATA PROTECTION REGISTRATION

We are registered as a data controller with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office and our data protection registration number is Z7369024.

##### SEVERABILITY

If a provision of this policy is determined by court or other competent authority to be unenforceable, the other provisions of this policy will continue in effect.
